Claren Moyers

Designer and Student

Claren is a current design student at the University of Texas at Austin focusing on designing interactions and experiences of all kinds. She is combining a graphics focused Design major with technical skills from fields such as information studies and computer science in order to align herself with a creative but structured education and future career.

Contact

Phone: (512) 905-5608

www:

Email: claren.moyers@gmail.com

Linkdin: Claren Moyers Instagram: @some.bathrooms

Soft Skills

Visual communication, design thinking, collaboration, creative problem-solving, youth leadership, punctuality, flexibility, thriving under deadlines, presenting/oral communication

Hard Skills

Adobe Suite:

Photoshop

Illustrator	••••
InDesign	••000
Premiere	••000
3D Modeling and Rendering:	
Autodesk Inventor	•••00
SketchUp	••000
Rhino	••000
Fusion360	••••
AutoCAD	•••00
HTML/CSS	••••
Python	•0000
Wire framing	••••
Hand Prototyping	••••

•••00

Passions

Hand Drafting

Sustainable and secondhand fashion, modeling (runway and editorial), podcast listening, cooperative living (student housing organization), walking and people watching, urban exploring, digital photography and editing

Education

High School Diploma **2017**:

Graduated from McCallum HS in Austin TX in the top 1% of the graduating class. Graduating GPA: 4.46 weighted

Design BFA 2017-2021:

Currently enrolled at the University of Texas with a major in Design and minor in information studies with a focus in human computer interaction.

Current GPA: 3.98

Experience

Cafe Teo and Gelato 2018-2019:

As a Barista and shift leader I have experience with money handling, customer service, and leadership responsibilities over other employees in order to run the day-to-day business.

Tandem Design Studio 2018-present:

I am a member at a student run design studio at UT Austin that completes design work as individuals and in teams for clients. The studio does both paid and unpaid work (for non-profit organizations).

Spark Magazine 2019-present:

I am a model and creative director on print photo shoots for the largest student run and published fashion magazine at UT Austin.

Convergent Build Team Member 2019-present:

I am currently working on the app UI/UX design and user research for SureWalk at the University of Texas. Convergent is a student run design and coding organization that solves real world issues through interfaces.

Modeling- Sue Weber Productions- Part-time 2018:

I have been coordinated by, but not contracted to, Sue Webber Productions for modeling events. Duties including showing up at call time fully prepared and being ready to adapt to the fast-paced environment and long hours of any production.

Kitchen Emloyee- Camp Emerald Bay 2017 (summer season):

I worked in an industrial scale kitchen which served on average 600 people per meal. I was able to learn skills about food prep, cooking, meeting customer needs, coordinating deliveries, organizing and storing stock, and maintaining code in a cramped environment.

Camp Counselor- Camp Emerald Bay 2015-2017 (seasonally):

As a counselor who taught a variety merit badges, I got to work with a diverse range of people from different regions, religions, ages, and interests. I gained skills in customer service and flexibility.